## logo subtext
Creative interior ideas

## menu
Home, hangAround (SUBMENU: White, Red, Black), hangOn, hangUp, Inspiration, Contact

————
Page: Hem/Home

## welcome text
Welcome to hangAround

The hangAround concept offers a smart and flexible way of hanging all your daily necessities like clothes, towels, blankets, and jackets. It is a trendy challenger of the commonly used hangers and shelfs.

## hangAround
A new product blending industrial roughness with minimalistic design. It truly offers a contrast to traditional design.

## hangOn
Very easy to extend. With available spare parts, additional hooks or wall fixtures can be mounted where ever You want. Vertically or horizontally? It's all up to you.

## hangUp
Standalone model, mounted on a base plate of proper oak.

————
Page: hangAround > White

White hangAround
Painted in a humble white, hangAround becomes one with its surrounding. Appealing and intriguing.

Like Meccano or other building kits, you can just as easy add more possibilities to hang Your clothes. One hangAround can easily be assembled with as many you would like. The flexibility is endless, and you can connect another hangAround on top or side by side.

Standard measurements: 100x30 cm.

Side by side or above, multiple kits will increase thereafter.

hangAround is made out of steel with a strong powder coating.

————
Page: hangAround > Red

Red hangAround
Thanks to the warmth and joy spread from its magnificent red, one cannot resist feeling a pleasure grow inside. A colour for those who dare.

Mounting a hangAround slightly tilted, gives all clothes and hangers extra space. By doing so, you can add more hangers on each beam and easily remove the one furthest in.

The placement of your unit is as flexible as hangAround itself. At home, you can place it in your master bedroom, entrance hall, bathroom, kitchen, laundry, or even outside on your balcony.

————
Page: hangAround > Black

Black hangAround
The black hangAround really retains the distinct industrial look. It demands your attention, speaks by itself, and claims its greatness.

As well as at home, it is suitable for any office space, shop, restaurant, and more.

Shop keepers have an exceptional alternative to expose their products by mounting hangAround directly in the sealing or suspending it from a beam.

————
Page: Inspiration

How would you like to use your unit?

————
Page: Kontakt/Contact

Kelvin! Add this sentence to the swedish page and let it look exactly the same, regardless what language it is!
"Note: For international contact or sales, please contact info@baeckstroem.com"